Guide to the Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program records 1969-2002.
Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program records 1969-2002
- Series VI. Publications and Resources
  - New York Cornell Cooperative Extension- EFNEP Guidelines, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - "Growing" - Educator's Guide and Appendices, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - "Growing" - preschoolers 3-5 years; toddlers 1-3 years; infants 0-12 months, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - "Creciendo" babies, toddlers, preschoolers, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - EFNEP Discussion Guides, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - "No Longer Hard to Reach" Discussion Guide and Reference Materials, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Theses and Reports Concerning CCE New York City Programs, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Understanding the Difference 4-H Clubs Make in the Lives of New York Youth, 1999-08 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - EFNEP - A Precedent - Setting Program by Muriel Brink, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - "It's All About Relationships"- A program resource notebook for childcare providers, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - "It's All About Relationships"- A program resource notebook for childcare providers, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Series VII. Slides, Photographs, and Videos
  - "Outreach Through Nutrition" - slide program (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Carbohydrate, Sugar, Starch and Fiber (slide set script) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Iron The Blood Building Nutrient (script and slides), 1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Iron The Hard To Get Nutrient (slide set script and slides), 1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Energy Our Food And Our Needs (slide set script and slides), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Aides - (slides), 1970-1979 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Food Stamp Program - (slides), 1980-1989 (Box 17, Folder 36-37)
  - Reaching and Teaching in Groups to Improve Cost Effectiveness - (slide set script), 1992-07 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - A Quarter Century of Making A Difference, 1969-1994; V - 11295 (Box 9)
  - In Step With EFNEP, 1990; V - 11294 (Box 9)
  - EFNEP at twenty-five, V - 6940 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP - Camp Casowasco, 1998; V - 6941 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP 30th Anniversary Celebration, 1999; V - 6942 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP "WPTZ" Plattsburgh - Focus 86, 1986; V - 6943 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP Participants Recruitment, 1994; V - 6944 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP - Helping People Learn and Do, V - 6945 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP - TNG, 1986; V - 6946 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP Participants Recruitment, 1994; V - 6947 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP -Working Smarter, V - 69448 (Box 16)
  - Master EFNEP 25 Years, V - 6949 (Box 16)
  - Master: EFNEP Spanish Version Education in Nutrition, V - 6950 (Box 16)
  - Spring Update EFNEP Camp Casowasco, 1998; V - 6951 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP Tape #1, 1992; V - 6952 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP Tape #2, 1992; V - 6953 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP Tape #3, 1992; V - 6954 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP Tape #4, 1992; V - 6955 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP Tape #5, 1992; V - 6956 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP Tape #6, 1992; V - 6957 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP Tape #7, 1992; V - 6958 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP Tape #8, 1992; V - 6959 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP Tape #9, 1992; V - 6960 (Box 16)
  - EFNEP Tape #10, 1992; V - 6961 (Box 16)
  - Inside My Mom: Nutrition During Pregnancy, tr. 9965a (Box 16)
  - Before the Baby is Born and Bottle Feeding, tr. 9966a (Box 16)
  - Food Recall and Working with Groups, tr. 9967a (Box 16)
  - Iron: The Hard to Get Nutrient, tr. 9968a (Box 16)
  - Outside My Mom - The story of a Breastfed Baby, tr. 9969a (Box 16)